Kanna...
柑菜は お前のこと 好きだぜ
loves you.
Tanigawa... loves me?
谷川が 俺のことを
Yeah.
Did she ask you to tell me that?
そう言ってくれって
谷川に頼まれたのか
No, this was my idea.
いや 俺の独断
Tanigawa loves Kaito...
谷川さんが海人君のこと
海人君は
What's Kaito going to do?
どうする気なんだろう
But Tanigawa didn't tell him herself...
けど 谷川さんから 直接告白されたわけじゃないし
I'll just have to act like nothing happened.
普段通りにしているしかないよね
Ishigaki...
石垣君 どうして海人君に
Why would you do that?
ああ 疲れた 疲れた
Man, I'm beat.
あれ いたの
Oh, I didn't see you there.
You're building that stuff again?
まーた 暗いことしてるわね
Did you get into another fight with Satoshi?
そっちはまた さとしさんと喧嘩
Nope!
違うわよ
I was going to go on a trip with some friends from high school,
高校時の仲間と旅行する予定だったんだけど
but then everyone had things come up.
急に皆の都合が悪くなってね
Even after I took the time to come back here...
せっかく帰ってきたのにさ
Oh.
そう
What's with you? You look upset.
何よ 元気ないわね
柑菜ちゃんと喧嘩でもした
Did you have a fight with Kanna or something?
What does Kanna have to do with this?
なんで 柑菜が出てくるんだか
何するんだ
What are you doing?!
I'll give you these. Go have fun with everyone.
あげる
皆で楽しんで来なよ
In Okinawa!
Seriously, Okinawa?!
へえ 沖縄
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作，仅供交流学习，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，请登录www.Kamigami.org
日听：秋水无痕 翻译：yaya 校对：小草爱吃梨 Syura 时间轴：小青
The day after tomorrow? For free?
明後日から ただで
Of course I'll go!
もちろん行く
I think my mom and dad'll let me go!
皆と一緒なら
ママやパパも許してくれると思うし
I'll call Lemon.
檸檬先輩には 俺から 連絡しとくから
You tell Mio and Kai.
美桜や 海 に知らせといてくるね
い いいけど
O-Okay...
This is your chance.
チャンスだな
Stop that!
や やめてってば
I told you to give it a rest!
そういうことナシって言ったでしょう もう
Well, see ya.
じゃね
Yes, Kirishima residence.
はい 霧島
えっ た 谷川
Tanigawa? Why are calling so late?
ど どうした こんな時間に
Tanigawa's calling?
谷川さんから
A trip?! To Okinawa?!
旅行 沖縄に
Tanigawa
え ああ なんだ そういうこと
Oh. So that's what you meant.
Sure.
うん 分かった
Okay. Later.
そうする じゃあ
今の電話 谷川さんから
Was that Tanigawa calling?
Yeah.
ええ 旅行に誘われて
I was invited on a trip.
Are you going?
行くの
I was thinking about it.
行こうと思いますけど
He's just going to go with her?!
そんな簡単に
Do you have any plans?
先輩 なんか予定入ってたり します
映画撮影も兼ねて
We'll all be going and filming the movie while we're there.
皆で行こうって
Oh, I see...
ああ そうなんだ
We'll be going to Okinawa.
旅行先 沖縄ですよ
ええ 沖縄
Okinawa?
This is Okinawa?!
こ これが沖縄
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
How can such a beautiful place be livrye'd?
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
こんな綺麗な場所がリブライされてるなんて
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Okinawa
Special!
The sea and beaches
are waiting for you!
Liv-rye?
リブライ
I don't really get it, but I guess you like it?
ええと よく分かんないけど
気に入りました
I do!
すごく
行きます
So you'll go?
絶対行く
I'm totally going!
When are we going? Tomorrow?
いつ行くの 明日 これから
I can't really put it into words, but I was really relieved when all of that happened.
うまく言えないけど
ああ すっごく嬉しい 楽しい
I can't wait! I'm so happy!
あの時の僕は
正直 ほっとしていた
難しいこと あんまり考えず
We could all just enjoy the trip together without any worries.
皆で旅行を楽しめばいいんだって
This summer's
そう思って
That's what I thought.
Can't believe I'm here.
来ちゃったな 沖縄
Yeah. I can't believe it either.
ああ 来ちゃったな
I'm feelin' it, though.
来てるぜ
Yeah, me too.
ああ 来てる
Feel what?
何が来てるの
Nothing, really.
What?
な 何
You look like you're trying hard.
いや 気合入ってるなって
そ そんなじゃないわよ
As if!
て 店員さんにこれ流行ってるって勧められて それで
One of the clerks said this is what's in right now, so...
Is that what happened?
そうだったかな
Mio!
美桜
Sorry! I was joking! It was a joke!
ごめん 嘘です 嘘でした 許して
It's fine. It looks good on you.
いいじゃん 似合ってるよ
ホント
Really?
Yeah.
Thanks.
ありがとう
Oh, you're welcome.
いや 別に
What swimsuit did you pick out, Mio?
美桜は どんな水着なんだ
Nothing special, really.
べ 別に普通のだよ
But my skin is sensitive, so I have to wear a sweatshirt...
でも 私 肌弱くて パーカー脱げないから
It's a shame with that body of yours.
せっかく スタイルいいのに
Don't stare at me!
あんまり 見ちゃダメ
で 先輩たちは
Where are Lemon and Ichika?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
お待たせ
Sorry,
ごめんなさい
it took a while to change into this.
ちょっと 着替えに手間取っちゃって
I'm sorry too.
お待たせ
来て よかったな
Glad you came here?
Totally.
What about me, Ishigaki?
石垣君 私はどうかしら
I'm sure someone out there appreciates you.
ある一定層には 効果があると思います
Am I ready to take on the world?
世界は狙える
Yamano.
Is it too skimpy?
ちょっと 大人っぽすぎるかな
Well, the world is a big place...
ああ すみません
Sorry! My sister only has stuff like that...
There have been several individuals who have made such a challenge.
姉さんの水着 そういうのしかなくて
I'm so grateful you let me borrow this!
Okay, this is getting old now.
貸してもらえて感謝してわ
I really had high expectations for this one.
かなり 覚悟ったのに
Don't give up!
ドンマイ
なんか 無駄に大作だな
This seems kind of needlessly large.
We're not done yet.
これから これから
What?
これから
海人君も埋めてあげようか
Kaito, how about we bury you too?
いや 俺はいいよ
Nah, I'll pass.
Isn't Kirishima acting kind of weird?
そう 楽しいのに
霧島君 なんか 様子が変な気しない
Maybe.
かもな
So what did you mean by "not done yet"?
ところで これからって
The tide is going to rise again soon, and then it'll look like it's floating, just like the real thing.
まっすぐ 潮が満ちるから
そしたら 本物みたいに水に浮かぶ
Let me outta here right now!
今すぐ出してくれ
Kai, help me!
海 助けて
Now that we've all had our share of fun in the ocean,
さって 沖縄の海も堪能したところで
撮影に入るわよ
let's start filming.
On our first day here?
初日から
I've come up with some ideas.
アイデアは練っておいたわ
迫る追手から逃れるために
The heroine hides out in Okinawa for a while to escape her pursuers.
ヒロインは一時的に沖縄に身を隠すの
How long did it take to come up with that?
そのアイデア本当に練ったんですか
I thought about it so much that I didn't sleep at all last night.
考え過ぎて 徹夜するほどにね
You certainly don't look it.
肌 ツヤツヤですよ
なんだか 注目されてるような
Everyone's kind of watching us...
That's because you're so beautiful.
それは あなたが美しいからよ
I don't think that's it.
いや そうじゃなくて
撮影許可とか取らなくていいんですか
Are you sure we don't need permission for this?
The sea belongs to no one, Tanigawa.
谷川さん 海は 誰のものでもないわ
I wash my hands of this.
知りませんよ
あのう 何してるんですか
Um, what are you doing?
ああ えっと 自主映画を
We're making a movie.
Amazing!
へえ すごい
Don't bother them, Kaori.
佳織 邪魔しちゃ悪いって
ちょっと聞いただけじゃん
I was just asking.
あれ もしかして 海ちゃん
Are you... Seaboy?
えっ なんで ガキん頃のあだ名を
Why do you know my old nickname?
It's really you!
あっぱり 私よ 私 佳織
It's me! I'm Kaori!
Kinoshita Kaori!
樹下佳織
Kinoshita... What?!
樹下 ってへえ 樹下 ホントに
Kinoshita? Really?
What?
何だ
Wow! It's been so long!
すごい 久しぶり
How many years has it been?
何年ぶりだろう
I knew it was you! You haven't changed at all!
でも すぐ分かったよ
だって ぜんぜん変わってないんだもん
That messy hair and those large glasses of yours.
その癖っ毛に大きなメガネ
樹下は だいぶ 変わったな
You've, uh... changed quite a bit.
Really?
そう まあ 高校に入ってから
Well, I've become a lot more feminine since I entered high school!
女子力高めましたから
But I never thought I'd see you here.
でも こんなとこで会えるなんて すっごい偶然
あ 本当
Yeah...
Kirishima, who is this?
霧島君 この方は
Oh, she's my elementary school...
ああ 俺の小学生ん時の
His fiancée!
婚約者です
婚
His...
約者
...fiancée?!
それは 興味ぶかい関係ね
What a fascinating relationship.
No, no!
違います ガキの頃 カップルを決めるような感じの遊びが流行ってて
When I was a kid, it was common for guys and girls to pretend they were couples.
She sat next to me, so everyone in our class made us out to be that way.
俺ら 席が隣同士だったから
クラスのやつらがそういう感じに仕立て上げて
That's not nice. I really believed it.
つれない 私はかなり本気だったのに
I gave you that letter during graduation, didn't I?
卒業式のとき 手紙あげたじゃない
You did?
そうだっけ
It's incredible that you've run into your first love again!
すごいじゃない
初恋の人と再会するなんて
I know, right?
やっぱり
And in Okinawa!
しかも 沖縄で
It's fate, isn't it?
運命的だよね
Hey, this is...
いや それは
Nice going, Kai.
やるね 海先生
So, what's your name?!
ああ あの お名前は
Ishigaki...
石垣 哲郎だけど
Tetsuro...
Ishigaki...
石垣さん
Do you have a girlfriend or something?
彼女とか いたりします
ああ いや いないけど
Not really...
Really? My name is Arisawa Chiharu!
そうですか
私 有沢千春で
Could you scoot back a little?
いい加減 離れてくれる
Oh, I see.
I don't wanna!
ええ いいんじゃん
Come on, please?
I love all these reactions.
皆 いい顔してるわ
Episode Six
You've got a rival.
What a lovely house!
素敵なお部屋よね
ご飯も美味しかったし
The food was really good too.
It was my first time eating barbecue.
私 バーベキュー って初めてだったわ
Really?
そうだったんですか
I'm really glad we could...
ホント 沖縄に来ることができて
...come to Okinawa.
良かったね
Right, Kaito?
海人君
そ そうですね
Yep.
What a twist of fate that you meet your classmate from elementary school.
しかも 小学校時代のクラスメートと運命的に出会えちゃうし
She's quite energetic and cute, don't you think?
活発で 可愛らしい人だったわね
結婚の約束までした 初恋の人との再会
What luck to be able to run into your first love, who you promised to get married to.
Pretty wonderful, right?
素敵なハプニングよね
She's not really my first love, you know...
あのう 初恋なんかじゃないですよ
She and I...
あいつとは
Takatsuki.
先輩
They sounded really close.
あいつ呼ばわりしましたよ
Almost like all that time never passed at all.
一瞬で二人の時間を埋めてしまったみたいね
There's nothing between Kinoshita and me...
いや 本当に樹下とは何もありませんから
Actually, why are you guys questioning me so much?
つうか 何で 俺 こんなに責められてるんだ
We're doing this
それは 貴月先輩が七海さんに
because Nanami asked Takatsuki
to look after you!
海人君のことをよろしくと頼まれているからです
We can't have you running off with some girl...
旅先で出会った女の子とのアバンチュールに身を委ねる
...you met on your vacation here!
なんてことをさせないためです
I'd never do that.
しませんって
Are you sure?
どうだか
Please just listen to what I have to say!
頼みますから 俺の説明を聞いてください
And now you're making up excuses.
言い訳するようなことをしたの
I'm not!
違います 事情の説明です
I'm trying to explain the situation.
That's what we call excuses!
情 情事
Just let me explain!
Sucks for Kai.
海人君のやつ 大変だな
What about you, Tetsuro?
哲郎君はどうなのかな
Huh?
何が
That Arisawa girl was really cute.
有沢さんって子 かなり可愛かったよ
She had a pretty nice body too.
スタイルも良かったな
アドレスも 交換してた
You even got her number.
I don't turn down requests from cute girls.
可愛い女の子の頼みは 断らないようにしてる
ホントですか
Really?
Wh—
ど どうして
What's going on?!
Allow me to introduce her.
紹介するわ
She'll be appearing in our movie. Her name is Kinoshita Kaori.
私たちの映画に出演してくれることになった
樹下佳織さんよ
Thanks for giving me this opportunity!
よろしくおねがいします
檸檬 どういうつもり
Lemon!
What are you doing?
I wanted a guest star for the Okinawa portion of the film.
沖縄編に ゲストが欲しかったの
I'm glad she came willingly.
快諾してくれて助かったわ
Somehow this feels very contrived...
すごく 作為的なものを感じるんですけど
She fit what I was thinking perfectly.
彼女は私のイメージにぴったりなの
That's exactly what I mean!
それが作為的なんです
What are you doing, Seaboy?
何してるの 海ちゃん
Besides, do you even know what "contrived" really means?
なんかの罰ゲーム
Did you lose a bet or something?
いや これは
No, I, uh...
What are you talking about?
Come on. Tell me.
でさ どっちが海ちゃんの恋人
Actually, you're just trying to change the subject!
Which one is your girlfriend?
None of them.
違うって そんなんじゃないよ
Really?
そうなんだ
だったら 映画出てもいいよね
Then I can be in the movie, right?
You're the director, right?
海ちゃん 監督なんでしょう
What are you filming?
どんなの撮るの
We're in Okinawa, so maybe everyone'll be in swimsuits?
やっぱ 沖縄だから 水着とか
あ そうだな
Hm, yeah...
No! I wasn't saying anything!
違います 何でもありません なんでも
Tetsuro, you were born on the 24th?!
哲郎さんは二十四日生まれなんですか
Your guardian tree is the apple tree, your guardian animal is the swan, and your guardian spirit is Étaín!
なら 守護樹は林檎 守護動物は白鳥
守護神はエーディンって事になりますね
You seem calm, cool, and older than you really are, but in reality, you're a delicate person.
冷静沈着な性格で
年齢よりも上に見られがちだけど
実はとても繊細な人なんです
That makes your ideal girl someone energetic who will pull you around. That sounds just like me, and—
その理想の相手となると
あなたを強引に引っ張って行くような大胆で快活な女性がいいらしいです
なんだか私と
Wow, those girls are something else.
すげえ 女の子たちだったな
Yep.
ああ でも 樹下のやつ
But Kinoshita wasn't like that before.
前はあんな感じじゃなかったのに
And now she wants to be in the movie...
しかも 映画に出るって
Tomorrow's shoot should be interesting.
楽しみだな 明日の撮影
Don't make fun of me!
おまえ 人をおちょくって
お休み
Sleep well.
Hey!
おい
Seriously.
ったく
ううん なんでもないの
Never mind.
なんか 調子狂っちゃって
I got too worked up there.
Stupid Kaito. He's not straightforward at all.
海人君め
全然 はっきりしないんだから
Being straightforward...
はっきりさせて
そしたら 私
That means...
I...
何考えてるんだか
What am I thinking?!
Thinking about this won't get me anywhere.
こんなこと考えたってしょうがないじゃない
I mean...
だって だって 私は
I...
You what?
私は
Lemon? How long have you been listening?
檸檬 いつから
I thought something smelled nice.
良い匂いがすると思って
Can I have some too?
私にも もらえるかしら
Sure, hold on.
ええ ちょっと待ってて
Do you want sugar?
えっと 砂糖は入れるんだっけ
No. But lots of milk.
要らないわ
でも ミルクはたっぷりね
ねえ イチカ
Hey, Ichika.
Well, you saw how those girls were acting,
あの子たちも大概だけど
but why don't you try being a little more forthright yourself?
あなたも少し素直になってみれば
郷に入っては郷に従えってことよ
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
あなた いったい
What are you talking about?
The Okinawan way, of course.
あら 沖縄流ってことよ
This won't work either.
これも 違う
まだ 決まらないの
You still can't decide?
These just aren't doing it for me, I guess.
なんかいまいち
こうピンと来ないっていうか
可愛いな 柑菜は
You're so cute, Kanna.
はあ 何それ ちょっ
What do you mean?
Good night!
お休み
Do you really have to sleep like that?
またそのまま寝るの
You know I have trouble falling asleep otherwise.
わ 私これじゃないと ちゃんと寝れないのを知ってるでしょう
Give him back!
彼を返して
Sure thing! If you're willing to come with me without a fight.
いいわよ
あなたが大人しく私に捕まればね
Who are you?
な 何者なの
You let people on this undeveloped planet know your true identity!
あなたは未開発のこの星で自分の正体を晒した
Therefore, I shall arrest you in
compliance with Federation law.
よって 連邦法に従い 私はあなたを拘束する
Are you a Galaxy Police Officer?!
銀 銀河警察のエージェント
And what if I am?
だとしたら
カット
Cut!
Acting is so difficult!
難しいね 演技って
Hey, let go, okay?
いいから 離れろって
You don't have to get so embarrassed!
照れなくてもいいじゃない
It's just hot!
暑いんだってば
熱くなければ イチャ付いてもいいの
So if it wasn't hot, you wouldn't mind me clinging?
That's not what I meant!
そういうんじゃなくて
You're blushing again!
もう 照れちゃって
I guess you can't help it.
しょうがないですね
そう
Right.
Lemon, when are we done filming?
れ 檸檬 後 どのくらい撮影するの
Let's see. I'd like to do five more scenes.
そうね あと五シーンらしいね
Oh... I see.
そ そう
美桜
Mio?
Filmmaking's so interesting, Tetsuro!
撮影って 面白いですね 哲郎さん
Really?
そ そう
I'm totally interested in it now.
私 断然興味が湧いてきちゃいました
檸檬先輩 コテージに小道具忘れたんで
Lemon!
I left a prop in the cottage. You think I could go grab it?
取りに行ってきていいっすか
Just hurry.
急いでね
All right!
了解
哲郎さん
Tetsuro!
That's weird.
なんか 意外 でれでれしまくるかと思ってたのに
I thought he'd be all over her by now.
That's because he's delicate.
繊細だから 哲郎君は
繊細 哲郎が
Tetsuro, delicate?
近くにいすぎるから 気付かないんだよ 柑菜は
You're with him too much, so you don't realize it.
うん そうかな
You think so?
Huh?
あれ 海人君と樹下さんは
Where are Kaito and Kinoshita?
あ ちっちゃいほうもいないわよ
The little one's gone too.
Are they...
ま まさか
Are they doing what?
まさかって
Use your imagination!
まさかですよ
まさか
They can't be!
What is it, Kinoshita?
で なんだよ 樹下
Why did you bring me here?
こんなとこを連れてきて
You already know, right?
分かってるでしょう
I wanted to be alone with you.
二人っきりになりたかったの
迷惑
Do you mind?
Is something wrong?
なんか あったの
いや 分かんないけど 妙にテンション高いし
I'm not really sure, but you're acting a lot more hyper than usual.
It's because I'm so happy to see you.
海ちゃんと会えてはしゃいじゃってるから
There you go again.
そのくせ
When you were a kid,
お前さ ガギんごろも
and something bad happened or you felt uncomfortable,
困ったこととか 都合悪いことあると
you put your finger on your lip.
そうやって 指咥えてたよな
Something's wrong, isn't it?
なんか あったんだろう
That's why you're forcing yourself to be with me.
だから 無理して その
俺に
If you want to talk about it...
良かったら 話してくれよ
And what if I'm serious?
本気なら
本気だとしたら
What if I'm serious?
What?
はい
So, what did I leave here...
えっと
忘れ物 忘れ物
Nothing, of course, but let's find something.
ホントはないけど
忘れ物
ま 適当に潰すか
I guess I'll just waste some time here.
Is that you, Kai?
おう 海か どうした まさかお前も
What's up?
You here for the same reason?
Did you find what you were looking for?
見つかりましたか 忘れ物
Arisa, why are you...
有沢さん どうして
I think you already know!
そんなの
決まってるじゃないですか
What if I
私が 本気で まだ 海ちゃんを好きだとしたら
really still like you after all this time?
そんな いきなり
But it's been so long...
時間なんて 関係ないでしょう
Time has nothing to do with it.
Last night, you said there wasn't anyone you like, right?
昨夜 好きな人いないって言ったよね
I...
それは
I said I wasn't dating anyone.
恋人がいないって言ったんだよ
好きな人は いるんだ
I do have someone I like.
割りと マジで
A lot.
So...
だから
ちょっ どうしたのかな
What are you doing, Arisa?
有沢さん
I'm quite selfish, you see.
私 結構わがままなんです
Really now?
そう なんだ
我慢も足りません
I can't hold myself back.
それに 肉食なんです
And I'm aggressive too.
You're surprisingly... strong...
ちょ ちょっと
意外に 力が
You shouldn't embarrass a girl.
女の子に
恥かかせないでください
No!
Where did they go?
どこ行っちゃったのよ もう
I started looking because I was caught in the moment,
勢いで来ちゃったけど
探して 私 どうするんだろう
but what am I gonna do when I find them?
海人君
Kaito?
美 桜
Mi... o?!
Sea... boy...
海ちゃん
樹 下
Kino... shita...
先 輩
Ichi... ka...
No one's...
誰も
帰ってこないわ
coming back.
Your Feelings.
Episode Seven
Tell me, Lemon. Tell me how Kaito feels!
I'm sure he's thinking about doing it.
Wow! As big as a horse!
教えろよ 檸檬
海人君の気持ちを
彼は きっと 何を考えてるわ
それは すごい 真奈美